Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Continuity Scripts
  - Satan's Satellites., 1952.; 2 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Judd Hldren, Aline Towne Wilson Wood, Lane Bradford
  - Satan's Satellites. CUT, 1952.; 4 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Judd Holdren, Aline Towne
  - Fort Dodge Stampede., 1951.; 8 copies. (Box 41)
  - Call the Mesquiteers., 1938.; 1 copy. (Box 41)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan, Max Terhune, Lynne Roberts
  - Gunfire at Indian Gap., 1957.; 9 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, Anthony George, George MacReady
    - Gunfire at Indian Gap. (trailer)., 1957; 18 copies.
  - The Wild Bunch of Wyoming and Harry Tracy (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 9 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Joe Sawyer, Slim Pickens
    - The Wild Bunch of Wyoming and Harry Tracy. (trailer)., 1954; 62 copies.
  - The Wild Frontier., 1947.; 5 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Jack Holt, Eddy Waller, Pierre Watkin
  - Wild Horse Ambush., 1952.; 3 copies. (Box 41)
  - Santa Fe Uprising., 1946.; 13 copies. (Box 41)
  - Singing Guns., 1950.; 2 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Vaughn Monroe, Ella Raines, Walter Brennan, Ward Bond
    - Singing Guns. (trailer)., 1950; 2 copies.
  - Frontier Investigator., 1949.; 9 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Roy Barcroft, Gail Davis
    - Frontier Investigator. (trailer)., 1949; 3 copies.
  - Fugitive from Sonora., 1943.; 4 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Don Red Barry, Wally Vernon, Lynn Merrick, Harry Cording
  - Gauchos of El Dorado., 1941.; 8 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Tom Tyler, Rufe Davis, Lois Collier, Duncan Renaldo
  - San Antone., 1953.; 4 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Arleen Whelan, Forrest Tucker, Katy Jurado
  - San Antone. CUT, 1953.; 2 copies. (Box 41)
    - San Antone. (trailer)., 1953; 9 copies.
  - Frontier Vengeance., 1940.; 1 copy. (Box 41)
    Cast: Don Red Barry, Betty Moran, George Offerman, Jr., Ivan Miller
  - Sun Valley Cyclone., 1946.; 3 copies. (Box 41)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Bobby Blake, Alice Fleming, Kenne Duncan
  - The Great Flamarion., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 42)
    Cast: Erich von Stroheim, Mary Beth Hughes, Dan Duryea
    - The Great Flamarion. (trailer)., 1945; 17 copies.
  - The Green Buddha., 1954.; 5 copies. (Box 42)
    Director: John LeMont
    Cast: Walter Rilla, Mary Merrall, Arnold Marle
    - The Green Buddha. (trailer)., 1954; 40 copies.
    - The Green Buddha. (Superimposed Spotted List - English Copy)., 1954; 2 copies.
  - Wolf of New York., 1940.; 3 copies. (Box 42)
    Director: William McGann
    Cast: Edmund Lowe, Rose Hobart, Jerome Cowan, William Demarest
  - Winter Serenade., 1944.; 6 copies. (Box 42)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, Vare Vague, Eugene Pallette, Robert Livingston
    - Winter Serenade. (trailer)., 1944; 15 copies.
  - Winter Wonderland., 1947.; 3 copies. (Box 42)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Charles Drake, Roman Bohnen, Renee Godfrey
    - Winter Wonderland. (trailer)., 1947; 19 copies.
  - Young and Wild., 1958.; 5 copies. (Box 42)
    - Young and Wild. (trailer)., 1958; 1 copy.
  - Young and Wild?. (CUT)., 1958 (Box 40)
  - Gangs of the Waterfront., 1945.; 3 copies. (Box 42)
    - The Gallant Legion., 1948.; 4 copies. (Box 41)
      Cast: William Elliott, Adrian Booth, Joseph Schildkraut
    - The Gallant Legion. (trailer)., 1948; 8 copies.
  - G.I. War Brides., 1946.; 27 copies. (Box 42)
    Cast: Anna Lee, James Ellison, Harry Davenport
  - Fugitive Lady., 1950.; 3 copies. (Box 42)
    Cast: Janis Paige, Binnie Barnes, Massimo Serato
  - Romance and Rhythm., 1940.; 2 copies. (Box 42)
    Cast: Kenny Baker, Frances Langford, Mary Boland, Ann Miller, Patsy Kelly, Phil Silvers, Hugh Herbert
  - Secret Service Investigator., 1948.; 1 copy. (Box 42)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Lloyd Bridges, George Zucco, June Storey
    - Secret Service Investigator. (trailer)., 1948; 7 copies.
  - The French Key., 1946.; 14 copies. (Box 42)
    Director: Walter Colmes
    Cast: Albert Dekker, Mike Mazurki, Evelyn Ankers, Byron Foulger
  - Underground Spy., 1950.; 16 copies. (Box 43)
  - The Undercover Woman., 1946.; 13 copies. (Box 43)
  - X Marks the Spot., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Damian O'Flynn, Helen Parrish, Dick Parrish, Dick Pursell
  - Rose of the Yukon., 1948.; 2 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Steve Brodie, Myrna Dell, William Wright
  - The Atomic Kid., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 43)
    Director: Leslie H. Martinson
    Cast: Mickey Rooney, Robert Strauss, Elaine Davis, Hal March
  - Women from Headquarters., 1950.; 3 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Virginia Huston, Robert Rockwell, Norman Budd
  - Rosie the Riveter., 1944.; 2 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Jane Frazee, Frank Albertson, Vera Vague, Frank Jenks
  - Earl Carroll Sketchbook., 1941.; 10 copies. (Box 43)
  - Follow Your Heart., 1936.; 8 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Marion Talley, Michael Bartlett, Nigel Bruce, Ben Blue, Luis Albert
  - Friendly Neighbors., 1940.; 1 copy. (Box 43)
    Cast: Weaver Brothers, Elviry, Lois Ranson, Spencer Charters
  - The Fighting Chance., 1955.; 1 copy. (Box 43)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Julie London, Ben Cooper, Taylor Holmes
    - The Fighting Chance. (trailer)., 1955; 24 copies.
  - The Fighting Devil Dogs., 1938.; 5 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Lee Powell, Herman Brix, Eleanor Stewart
  - The Flying Squadron., 1952.; 5 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Massimo Serato, Dina Sassoli, Umberto Spadaro
  - Frisco Waterfront., 1935.; 10 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: Ben Lyon, Helen Twelvetrees, Rod LaRoque, James Burke
  - Out of the Storm., 1948.; 2 copies. (Box 43)
    Cast: James Lydon, Lois Collier, Marc Lawrence, Byron Foulger
  - Out of the Storm. CUT, 1948.; 9 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: James Lydon, Lois Collier, Marc Lawrence, Richard Travis
    - Out of the Storm. (trailer)., 1948; 4 copies.
  - Navajo Trail Raiders., 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Robert Emmett Keane
  - Wyoming Outlaw., 1939.; 1 copy. (Box 44)
    Cast: John Wayne, Ray Corrigan, Raymond Hatton
  - Arizona Manhunt., 1951.; 4 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Michael Chapin, Eilene Janssen, James Bell
  - The Outcast., 1954.; 3 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: John Derek, Joan Evans, Jim Davis, Catherine McLeod
    - The Outcast. (trailer)., 1954; 13 copies.
  - Rough Riders of Cheyenne., 1945.; 6 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Peggy Stewart, Mira McKinney, Monte Hale
  - The Last Musketeer., 1951.; 2 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Mary Ellen Kay, Slim Pickens, Monte Montague
    - The Last Musketeer. (trailer)., 1951; 22 copies.
  - Prisoners in Petticoats., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Valentine Perkins, Robert Rockwell, Danni Sue Nolan, Anthony Caruso
    - Prisoners in Petticoats. (trailer)., 1950; 1 copy.
  - El Paso Stampede., 1953.; 1 copy. (Box 44)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Phyllis Coates, Stephen Chase
  - Frontier Investigator., 1949.; 7 copies. (Box 44)
  - The Outcast., 1954.; 4 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: John Derek, Joan Evans, Catherine McLeod, Ben Cooper, Slim Pickens
  - Frisco Tornado., 1950.; 11 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Martha Hyer, Stephen Chase
    - Frisco Tornado. (trailer)., 1950; 21 copies.
  - Brimstone., 1949.; 3 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Adrian Booth, Walter Brennan, Forrest Tucker
  - Oregon Trail., 1945.; 9 copies. (Box 45)
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Peggy Stewart, John Merton, Mary Carr
  - Hoosier Holiday., 1943.; 2 copies. (Box 45)
    Cast: Hoosier Hot Shots, The Music Maids, George D. Hay
  - Terror at Midnight., 1956.; 9 copies. (Box 45)
    Cast: Scott Brady, Joan Voh, Frank Faylen
    - Terror at Midnight. (trailer)., 1956; 16 copies.
    - Terror at Midnight. (Superimposed Spotted List - English Copy)., 1956; 5 copies.
  - Under Western Stars., 1938.; 1 copy. (Box 45)
    Cast: Guy Usher, Tom Chatterton, Kenneth Harlan
  - Old Oklahoma Plains., 1952.; 6 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Rex Allen and KOKO the Miracle Horse of the Movies
  - Old Oklahoma Plains. CUT, 2 copies. (Box -)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Slim Pickens, Elaine Edwards
  - Down Dakota Way., 1949.; 7 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Roy Rogers and Dale Evans
  - Web of Danger., 1947.; 15 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Adele Mara, Bill Kennedy
  - Roll on Texas Moon., 1946.; 7 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Dale Evans
  - Roll on Texas Moon. CUT, 1946.; 8 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Dale Evans, Dennis Hoey
  - Roll On Texas Moon. CUT, 1946.; 1 copy. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers and Trigger
  - Roll On Texas Moon. (CUT)., 1946; 1 copy. (Box *)
  - Heart of the Rockies., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Penny Edwards, Gordon Jones, Ralph Morgan
  - Heart of the Rockies. (CUT)., 1951; 10 copies.
  - Sons of the Pioneers., 1942.; 5 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, George 'Gabby' Hayes
  - Winter Serenade., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, Eugene Pallette Vera Vague
  - Under Western Stars., 1938.; 6 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Smiley Burnette, Carol Hughes
  - Eyes of Texas., 1948.; 5 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Lynne Roberts, Andy Devine, Nana Bryant
    - Eyes of Texas. (trailer)., 1948; 2 copies.
  - Under Western Stars., 1938.; 8 copies. (Box 47)
  - Utah., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, George Gabby Hayes
  - Under Nevada Skies., 1946.; 1 copy. (Box 47)
  - San Fernando Valley., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Dale Evans
  - Young Buffalo Bill., 1940.; 10 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes
  - Bells of Rosarita., 1945.; 4 copies. (Box 47)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Dale Evens
  - Southward Ho., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Mary Hart, Gabby Hayes
  - South of Caliente., 1951.; 4 copies. (Box 48)
  - Jesse James at Bay., 1941.; 14 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Gale Storm, Sally Payne
  - Young Buffalo Bill., 1940.; 2 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Pauline Moore, Hugh Sothern
  - Sheriff of Tombstone., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Elyse Knox, Addison Richards
  - Idaho., 1943.; 5 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Smiley Burnette
  - South of Santa Fe., 1942.; 18 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Paul Fix
  - Song of Arizona., 1956.; 15 copies. (Box 48)
  - Sunset Serenade., 1942.; 8 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, George Hayes
  - Sunset On the Desert., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 48)
  - The Far Frontier., 6 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Andy Devine
  - San Fernando Valley., 1944.; 1 copy. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Dale Evans, Jean Porter, Andrew Tombes
  - Wall Street Cowboy., 1939.; 10 copies. (Box 48)
  - Susanna Pass., 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 48)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, DaleEvans
  - Sunset in El Dorado., 1945.; 3 copies. (Box 48)
  - Grand Canyon Trail., 1948.; 1 copy. (Box 49)
  - Grand Canyon Trail. CUT, 1948.; 4 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Jane Frazee, Andy Devine, James Finlayson
    - Grand Canyon Trail. (trailer)., 1948; 6 copies.
  - Spoilers of the Plains., 1950.; 7 copies. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Penny Edwards
  - Springtime In The Sierras., 1947.; 2 copies. (Box 49)
  - Bells of Rosarita., 1945.; 1 copy. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Dale Evans, Adele Mara
  - Song of Texas., 1943.; 1 copy. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Sheila Ryan
  - Song of Nevada., 1945.; 2 copies. (Box 49)
  - On the Old Spanish Trail., 1947.; 2 copies. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Tito Quizar, Jane Frazee, Andy Devine
  - On The Old Spanish Trail. CUT, 1947.; 4 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Tito Guizar, Jane Frazee, Andy Devine, Estelita Rodriguez
  - Pals of the Golden West., 1951.; 3 copies. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers and his wife Trigger, Dale Evans, Estelita Rodriguez
  - Pals of the Golden West. CUT, 1951.; 3 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Dale Evans, Estelita Rodriguez, Pinky Lee
    - Pals of the Golden West. (trailer)., 1951; 20 copies. (Box *)
  - Young Bill Hickok., 1940.; 7 copies. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Jacqueline Wells, Monte Blue
  - North of the Great Divide., 1950.; 1 copy. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Trigger, Penny Edwards
  - Days of Jesse James., 1939.; 3 copies. (Box 49)
  - Night Time in Nevada., 1948.; 5 copies. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Adele Mara, Andy Devine, Grant Withers
    - Night Time in Nevada. (trailer)., 1948; 2 copies.
  - Night Time In Nevada IN TRUCOLOR IN TRUCOLOR.( CUT!), 1958.; 21 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Adle Mara, Andy Devine
  - Night Time In Nevada. CUT, 1948.; 1 copy. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Trigger, Adele Mara
  - Come On Rangers., 1938.; 12 copies. (Box 49)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Mary Hart
  - Circus Girl., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 49)
    Director: Herbert J. Yates (P)
    Cast: Kristina Soederbaun, Willy Birgel
  - Rough Riders' Round-up., 1939.; 10 copies. (Box 50)
  - Rough Riders' Round-up. CUT, 1939.; 8 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Mary Hart, Raymond Hatton, Eddie Acuff
  - Utah., 1945.; 8 copies. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Dale Evans, Peggy Stewart
  - Lights of Old Santa Fe., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 50)
  - Under Western Stars., 1938.; 4 copies. (Box 50)
  - North of the Great Divide., 1950.; 1 copy. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Penny Edwarda, Gordon Jones
  - Rainbow over Texas., 1946.; 23 copies. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Sheldon Leonard
  - The Far Frontier., 5 copies. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Trigger, Gail David, Andy Devine
  - On the Old Spanish Trail., 1947.; 10 copies. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Tito Guizar, Andy Devine, Estelita Rodriguez
    - On the Old Spanish Trail. (trailer)., 1947; 1 copy.
  - My Pal Trigger., 1946.; 3 copies. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Dale Evans, Jack Holt
  - Grand Canyon Trail., 1948.; 10 copies. (Box 50)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Jane Frazee, Andy Devine, Robert Livingston
  - Young Bill Hickok., 1940.; 2 copies. (Box 51)
  - In Old Cheyenne., 1941.; 1 copy. (Box 51)
  - Heart of the Golden West., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 51)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Ruth Terry, Walter Catlett
  - Shine on Harvest Moon., 1944.; 1 copy. (Box 51)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Mary Hart, William Farnum
  - Shine on Harvest Moon. CUT, 1948.; 1 copy. (Box *)
  - San Fernando Valley., 1944.; 1 copy. (Box 51)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Dale Evans, Jean Porter
  - Man from Oklahoma., 1945.; 3 copies. (Box 51)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Dale Evans, Roger Pryor
    - Man from Oklahoma. (trailer)., 1945; 30 copies.
  - Man from Cheyenne., 1952.; 19 copies. (Box 51)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Sally Payne, Lynne Carver
  - Sons of the Pioneers., 1942.; 3 copies. (Box 51)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Chester Conklin
  - Sons of the Pioneers. CUT, 1942.; 15 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Gabby Hayes, Maris Wilson, Minerva Urecal
  - Pals of the Golden West., 1951.; 3 copies. (Box 51)
  - In Old Amarillo., 1941.; 2 copies. (Box 51)
    Director: William Witner
    Cast: Roy Rogers, Estelita Rodrigues, Penny Edwards, Pinky Lee
  - My Pal Trigger., 1946.; 6 copies. (Box 51)
    - My Pal Trigger. (trailer)., 1946; 10 copies.
  - Melody Ranch., 1940.; 10 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Jimmy Durante Anne Miller, Barton Maclane
  - Round Up Time in Texas., 1936.; 7 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Maxine Doyel
  - Round Up Time in Texas. CUT, 1936.; 6 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Maxine Doyel, Le Roy Mason
  - Rootin' Tootin' Rhythm., 1937.; 5 copies. (Box 52)
    Director: [? Gene Autry]
    Cast: Smiley Burnette, Monte Blue Al Clauser and His Oklahoma Outlaws
  - Rootin' Tootin' Rhythm. CUT, 1937.; 4 copies. (Box *)
    Director: ?
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Armida, Monte Blue
  - Western Jamboree., 1938.; 3 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Brunette
  - Prairie Moon., 1938.; 7 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Smiley Burnette, Walter Tetley, David Gorcey
  - Springtime in the Rockies., 1937.; 13 copies. (Box 52)
  - The Sagebrush Troubadour., 1935.; 5 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Antry, Barbara Pepper, Smiley Burnette
  - Mountain Rhythm., 1939.; 8 copies. (Box 52)
    Director: B. Reaves Eason
  - Twilight On the Rio Grande., 1947.; 6 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Sterling Holloway, Adele Mara, Bob Steele
  - Trail to San Antone., 1947.; 10 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Peggy Stewart Sterling Hollowey
  - Saddle Pals., 1947.; 3 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Aurey, Sterling Holloway
  - South Of the Border., 1939.; 5 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, William Farnum, Duncan Reynaldo
  - Boots and Saddles., 1937.; 5 copies. (Box 52)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Judith Allen, Ra Hould
  - Star Dust On the Sage., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 52)
  - Oh, Susanna!., 1936.; 16 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Frances Grant, CLARA KIMBALL YOUNG!
  - Oh, Susanna. (trailer). CUT, 1936; 1 copy. (Box 53)
  - Oh, Susanna!., 1936.; 3 copies. (Box 53)
  - Ridin' on a Rainbow., 1941.; 1 copy. (Box 53)
    Director: Lew Landers
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Mary Lee, Carol Adams
  - Robin Hood of Texas., 1947.; 2 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Lynne Roberts, Sterling Holloway
  - Robin Hood of Texas. CUT, 1947.; 4 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Lynne Roberts, Sterling Holloway, Adele Mara
  - The Sagebrush Troubador., 1935.; 2 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Barbara Pepper, Smiley Burnette
  - Sunset in Wyoming., 1941.; 6 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, George Cleveland
  - Sunset in Wyoming. CUT, 1941.; 9 copies.
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, George Cleveland, Monte Blue
  - The Old Corral., 4 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Hope Manning
  - Ride Ranger Ride., 1946.; 2 copies. (Box 53)
  - Ride Ranger Ride. CUT, 7 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Brunette (!), Kay Hughes, Monte Blue, George Lewis
  - The Singing Vagabond., 1935.; 3 copies. (Box 53)
    Director: Carl Pierson
    Cast: Ann Rutherford, Nileo Welch, Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette
  - Back in the Saddle., 1941.; 4 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Mary Lee, Edward Norris
  - Blue Montana Skies., 1939.; 7 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, June Storey, Harry Woods
  - Man from Music Mountain., 1938.; 16 copies. (Box 53)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Carol Hughes, Sally Payne
  - Man from Music Mountain. CUT, 1938.; 3 copies. (Box *)
  - Ride, Tenderfoot, Ride., 1940.; 1 copy. (Box 53)
  - Sierra Sue., 1941.; 1 copy. (Box 54)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Fay McKenzie, Frank Thomas
  - Heart of the Rio Grande., 1942.; 5 copies. (Box 54)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Fay McKenzie, Edith Fellows
  - Mexicali Rose., 1939.; 6 copies. (Box 54)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Noah Beery, William Farnum
  - Yodelin' Kid from Pine Ridge., 1937.; 10 copies. (Box 54)
  - Rovin' Tumbleweeds., 1939.; 4 copies. (Box 54)
  - Melody Trail., 1935.; 5 copies. (Box 54)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Ann Rutherford, Smiley Burnette
  - Melody Ranch., 1940.; 2 copies. (Box 54)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Jimmy Durante, Ann Miller, Vera Vague, Jerome Cowan
    - Melody Ranch. (trailer)., 1940; 1 copy.
  - Red River Valley., 1936.; 4 copies. (Box 54)
    Director: B. Reeves Eason
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Frances Grant, Booth Howard
  - Git Along Little Dogies., 1937.; 5 copies. (Box 54)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Judith Allen
  - The Singing Cowboy., 1936.; 1 copy. (Box 54)
    Director: Mack Wright
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Louis Wilde, Lon Chaney Jr.
  - This World of Ours - Hong Kong., 7 copies. (Box 55)
    Director: Carl Dudley (p)
    Cast: ---
  - The Sponge Diver (short subject)., 1 copy. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Egypt., 1951.; 21 copies. (Box 55)
    Director: Carl Dudley (prod.)
  - This World of Ours - France., 1 copy. (Box 55)
    Cast: documentary
  - This World of Ours - France (Dudley Pictures Corporation) (travel film). CUT, 1 copy. (Box 55)
  - This World Of Ours - France (travel film). CUT, 1 copy. (Box 55)
    Director: Carl Dudley (P)
  - This World Of Ours - Sweden., 1950.; 15 copies. (Box 55)
    (travel film).
  - This World of Ours - Philippines (travel film)., 1952.; 33 copies. (Box 55)
    Cast: -------1952
  - This World of Ours - Thailand., 1954.; 23 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Venezuela (travel film)., 1955.; 25 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Turkey., 1955.; 2 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - London. (travel film)., 1950; 16 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - London., 1950.; 5 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Northwest Adventure (travel film)., 1956.; 25 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - England., 1951.; 23 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World Of Ours- Formosa (travel film)., 21 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Portugal., 21 copies. (Box 55)
    Director: Carl Dudley (Prod.)
  - This World of Ours - Glacier National Park., 14 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Norway (travel film)., 1950.; 18 copies. (Box 55)
    Cast: -----
  - This World of Ours - Spain., 1950.; 13 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Greece., 21 copies. (Box 55)
  - Miracle in Venezuela (travel film)., 1956.; 35 copies. (Box 55)
    Director: M.V. Tinoeo and R. Borges Villegas
  - This World of Ours - Italy., 1951.; 22 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World Of Ours - Chile (travel film)., 1952.; 6 copies. (Box 55)
    Director: Carl Dudley (P)P
  - This World of Ours - Belgium., 1951.; 24 copies. (Box 55)
  - This World of Ours - Singapore (travel film)., 1953.; 11 copies. (Box 55)
    Cast: _____
  - This World of Ours - Puerto Rico (travel film)., 1952.; 6 copies. (Box 55)
    Director: Dudley, Carl (P)
  - This World of Ours - Switzerland., 24 copies. (Box 55)
  - Man With The Steel Whip (Serial episodes 1-12)., 1954. (Box 56)
    Cast: Richard Simmons, Barbara, Bestar
  - Enemies of the Universe (Commando Cody No.1)., 1953.; 3 copies. (Box 56)
  - Atomic Peril (Commando Cody No. 2)., 1953.; 18 copies. (Box 56)
  - Nightmare Typhoon (Commando Cody No.4)., 1953.; 4 copies. (Box 56)
  - Commando Cody no.4 Nightmare Typhoon. CUT, 1953.; 1 copy. (Box 56)
  - Destroyers of the Sun (Commando Cody No. 6)., 1953.; 4 copies. (Box 56)
  - Robot Monster Of Mars (Commando Cody No.7)., 1953.; 3 copies. (Box 56)
  - Captives of the Zero Hour (Commando Cody No.12)., 1953.; 1 copy. (Box 56)
    Cast: Judd Holdren, Aline Towne, Richard Crane
  - The Vigilantes Are Coming (episode 6)., 9 copies. (Box 56)
  - Federal Operator 99 (serial). Episodes 1-3, 6-12., 1945; 1 ea. (Box 56)
    Director: Spencer Bennett, Wallace A. Grissell, Yakima Canutt
    Cast: Marten LaMont, Helen Talbot
    - Federal Operator 99 (serial). Episodes 1-3, 6-12 (trailer)., 1945; 18 copies. (Box 56)
  - The Tiger Woman. [Episodes 1-12]., 1944; 2 copies. (Box 56)
    Director: Spencer Bennet, Wallace Grissell
    Cast: Allan Lane, Linda Stirling Duncan Renaldo
  - King of the Carnival. - serial, episodes 1-12. CUT, 1955; 1 copy. (Box *)
    Cast: Harry Lauter, Fran Bennett Gregory Gay
    - King of the Carnival. (trailer)., 1955; 12 copies. (Box *)
  - King of the Carnival (episodes no.1 and 2)., 1955.; 2 copies. (Box 56)
    Cast: Harry Lauter, Fran Bennett
  - The Mardi Gras (short subject). CUT, 1950.; 10 copies. (Box *)
  - The Three Minnies (Cartoon in Trucolor)., 1958.; 34 copies. (Box 56)
    Director: Leonard Levinson
  - The Quiet Man., 12 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: John Wayne, Maureen O'Hara, Barry Fitzgerald, Ward Bond
    Missing Material
    Script missing 4/4/2024 (SE).
  - The Quiet Man. (Box 22)